and then in this video we will do
nothing but specify and highlight things
that had already been addressed in the
previous videos those who have already
followed us surely know us and more or
less know the topics we deal with
and that's what we share in
a very humble way simple and then we
find ourselves here with salvatore and
not in naples and our friend pino
cammarata in such a way as to repeat to
make more clarity
lately a video has been published
the video is about
breast cancer and where salvatore talks
with maria which is also called
infinite joy and is a video where you try
to give information explaining the
purification path of this lady
who came to know us and in
particular salvatore has been
following her for quite a few months more than
two months if not erro is definitely
more than two months because it started
winter at his house may have been that
he needed to be followed so
m much more constant up to taking
but who has made the decision to
move so here if I have been here it has
almost reached the end of these 40
days of purification in short I do not repeat
what has already been said in the video
but the fact is that this video has
aroused many harsh and bitter criticisms,
among other things, free I would say against
not only the lady but also the
savior on doing because if
the topic of
intestinal parasites was taken up, the fact
that salvatore plagiarized the lady was raised it
was said that savior he poses himself
defines himself as a teacher like a wall or
even puts himself at the same
level as jesus christ
these are all
free critical disinformation I repeat that they have been
made towards very
simple people numbers I personally have been
attending the house of savior paladin for
almost five years and there is
only one person who has called him a teacher
or a guru or I don't know what else has never
been to the ba mbini
even give him the you he
himself has always ended up in the videos
at least those who know us
can confirm him as a semi-
illiterate ignorant even
troglodyte it is certainly strange that a
person who calls himself ignorant and
manages to talk to face certain
speeches becere in effects is
contradictory paradoxical in some
respects but in life not everything that
is known is learned from books or from
having obtained titles and the
like so we will continue to pursue
this path regardless of the
stupidity of others from the lack of
delicacy and respect
instead of trying to understand instead
simply and exclusively try to
attack
we will continue indeed we will provide further details
documentation regarding the speech of
parasites because really almost all
the people who wanted to share
the path of purification through
therapeutic fasting have done
nothing but evacuate and spend
intestinal parasites of a certain
entity up to even over 40 50 60
days so this is a fact that we
can prove but surely the
stupid ones will have the opportunity to challenge even
the photographs that people have
taken because there are very
clear photographs and obvious and explicit that
I speak but surely the tractors and
deceivers will do other than
say surely they are retouched with
photoshop they have been taken from the internet
and so on we know
this is the environment of the web everyone
can say anything but I repeat
aside ours is simply wanting
to clarify especially for those
who have ears to hear
and then and now let's pass the word
I had not read in such a way that we
can not once again with maybe
further details tell his
personal experience is the how and the
because he met
salvatore paladino through pino camparada then what
happened what and it was the reason
why you came here the reason is that
at some point my life having
being sort of a problem
concerning my health or seeds but the
classical path of classical medicine
however I was going completely astray
I was close at my so-called end it is a
sought having known lapino cammarata
of the existence of salvatore paladino
I have tried in every way of power between
recalibrating you and getting in touch with
a savior paladin also pino
Campagna from I replied what
stands out was and there it must be said that on Saturday the
baladin had suffered a
physical attack of considerable entity for which he was
unable just at that moment
I had that to stay silent to be able to
listen to myself at a certain point then
the moment came, luckily for me, that I was able to
speak with the design the
moment from the moment we are of the
sandwich came back to his house
the opportunity was to me, let's say to myself,
even though he had not yet recovered
exactly that energy that
would really allow him to be able to
sit down to be able to give himself again the
other 100 alessandro antico torches
despite everything through the
friendship program song di pino you
managed to get a city anyway to speak
for my part they listened to let you
listen to savior paladin and
known staff I met an
exceptional person on the level
above all one as well as on the level
of his wisdom who is not
necessarily to bind cultures
as to say sealed by degrees or
anything else and through his
suggestions
often and willingly especially in the
first very energetic phase because
salvatore paladino is like this and must be accepted
as well as we must ethical molten what does
energies mean in the sense that given
my
very weak environmental psychological situation, he tried to
sound internal in a very many
energies that he saw and understood
above all that i was a
very dangerous situation for my own
survival and energetically
lasted me despite the fact that he needed more
energy for the reason that he said
before it was all he had already
feared in fact the Pope Beppino
himself said or he could also confirm
that every time he received savior
despite he could talk to you
then salvatore after accompanied because he
sees in naples he needed
my partner support for a comparison
of the hours and I came too and when then
salvatore with nino volleyball hollow and
told him he shouldn't do
then when he came to naples he went away
poor savior returned to
being what he was before he was not
healed even could no longer speak
but in the bond and in the presence to hold a
saving offering he gave him suggestions and
what he needed energy and energy to
hear exactly that he does now the speech
of which was raised by others ie
his his being as well as saying the
alpone define him violent for because he
expresses himself with unorthodox non-diplomatic count maine
and you in any case this is
his being violent as
others define it to you as an
assorted effect subtitle as I said
before an energizing effect in the sense
that although he did not have the energy
for reasons he will be there today he had told us
before to give help to others he
found almost by magic when he
spoke he spoke with me because he
saw a situation in me inside of me
the situation is very very precarious and
he found himself and appealed to all
his human resources as well as energy
to give help especially to me because he
understood I do not call him his
condition that you needed that I needed
him more than he needed to
find your car shopping in Palermo
that even not having over sticks then
you say something that when a
person needs to get involved with other
things the
savior feels pain inside the heart
when you have children suffering when
av ye people who got sick
were first massacred and everything is
a pain that I have suffered in my
family and if I continue in this
way I love her with pain and the
trait of savior effecting to
salvation damage are you going to people
in in this way, suffering and sometimes
crying with pain of not being
able to be able to help all those
who need it are at this point
something special happens like in
a pressure cooker when the charge
at the level of exploding and there is the
valve my hand palate
unfortunately it is tony g torino that a
loose dog a game fingers that anyone
can make a deck so is the moment in which he
comes out hard he comes out to defend himself and
stuff from what I defended
myself I said all those things in the videos
because anyone I can would have done me
worse
so when you and a pinch the
good being mentally that
we didn't play yourself I gave
that ca he draws that strength from the course that
you came with him because he was
afraid to come here under mentis alone he is
practically substituted for my psyche it
is very weak and since it was
found to yourself it was a ritual it
was more manifested with you had it more
absolute who is savior a no
account racism in fact this dualism
of the turiddo person and savior in
the say they tell you all about what is
the true nature of a savior paladin
which is certainly not what is
referred to by fools
by those who instead it has as its sole
objective only to demolish the
work of others
then for example we have known each other with pine
for about 40 years
yes because the first time you are very much
a cousin with a relative of yours
because having the first time with the vote
for I embrace you that in gangrene
and the doctors in short, if it puts a lot of
thia, they would have it so many
now one of concern
1 you should not be pissed off when
I would certainly keep one thing I cannot to
play it semi-illiterate latita
ignorant and or luminary of science
terror of
course you must not be pissed off must not
be pissed off
I must not be pissed off when at
11 hello while someone who
shot me here I had a detachment of a
detachment of the glass in the Rete rita acuta
an 11-year-old boy in Palermo
have removed his eyeball and I or
through salvatore all those who have
had such a problem are also
on the video that they have made
statements such as santana pole and
frost sicurella as the sister of his
aunt that the Czech who had the
corneas fallen because if it was burned with
bleach
now she sees us and sees little in a short
time she regained her sight and the
best with she told him that I had to
do when they would have
found the horns a knowing that
surely would not have succeeded for how it
had to be optimal now he sees us
priest better than before
now when I notice best and what on my
skin who ruined my life as a
child for a restrained buda that
i cured worse things then bigger things
club like all kinds of
all measures for the eyes
what to do i must not be
pissed when they kill my mother
deliberately they must not being
pissed off when they murdered my
sister in an institution that paid 60
euros a day to be looked after
and they tied her up and the year and to put
the diaper they broke his legs
and then after the operation is
all the sleeping pill who gave him
everything when she died then you were
murdered by official medicine
that is I must not be pissed I must not
say what they did to me when the
doctor burned my life that is with
a massive dose of cortisone I must not
be pressed I must not say that
what are i
what i would do i was and for a child course
for a driving license course for borgio part
of force but you would not be pissed off i
did not react go and shoot co
others do me
i'm
just pissed off nonino salvatore
turin defending saved the savior he
would already be very afraid of heartbreak
this is my life when I
met him I voted him then he
took me to your father who had tamed the
wall I changed how many he was 75 years old
70 80 but you want to make a fire of
sant'antonio
then he took the fund it was that he
hopes a very simple thing simple way
without without merits and snacks
now how do you do none 6 pissed off when
I am nobody I can do
all these miracles giving information
is information because everything
you have done i will do it
at home your mother helped your father and
your you so careful yourself
according to my information i never said i
am a weather so it is
just fine however, however, always
highlight it to avoid that it can
be misunderstood because the do and
misunderstanding is always around
the corner behind the door
it is only and exclusively a
sharing of information enough there
is no therapist here no
thaumaturge no alchemist no
healer if only in izmir and on a doctor
to no one menal of
exact science there is simply a person
who is informed due to particular
vicissitudes of life that he has
experienced on himself is that
through the experience lived on
himself I have done nothing but
share it and obtaining those results
that can be inferred from the
testimonies both video and in writing
but those videos are much more extensive
then just to be tell an
anecdote about nino napoli it
happened and nino having learned in the months
preceding the previous year of the
massacre suffered as a savior by as a
savior with our small
contribution he managed to overcome
what for doctors was absolutely
unsurpassable because doctors l 'they had
condemned when they
viewed the tac no n there is hope
because with three but tommy one of 9 cm and
with you are not and one of three and a half we are
talking about centimeters not mm in that
state there could be no
chance no hope of life and
above all because savior in the first place and
we in agreement with him there was the
categorical refusal of any
emergency surgery
mindful of these facts eno napoli even
if he did not live directly because he
still did not know us by virtue
anyway because of what had
happened that which is happened in
recent months to michael schumacher with
the accident he had, he considered it
appropriate to do something that will now
explain the area location of the experience
personally no one from the promoter
so if when on Saturday I want to say
something to make the speech of
also as I had him yes then
savior it is good to specify one thing and
as perhaps the already said savior
when he was attacked in a mortal way
I want to take to his house and st ato also
hit
the only one violently in one eye also because the other one they had
removed as a child it was
exact for ivan and they did not
touch him so in addition to being others
there must be a very big damage
level the report there was also damage
to the 'eye so much that he reported a
swelling as can be seen from the
medical records he did not see he
did not see he did not know how you do not tell me
how because I do not know he also
signed documents exist affirmed he
answered the doctors' questions he
refused I repeat any intervention
of medicine there are medical
records tac medical reports that can
absolutely document any
track cut esophagus I could not
speak yet he says that I was speaking I
do not know if because I do not know these things
so with them it is after all
what has fallen we cannot do other
than to tell what happened
said this nino considered it appropriate
to apologize but 25 points are no longer
seen even that the scar the dog gas box
and what was woken up by itself has closed
but I repeat this will have the way the
detractors if there are still some
because like St. Thomas if I do not see I do not
think they will be able to see
since they do not believe
it is possible win everything from the report minds
that from beta we have already entered the kings we will
insert once again in such a way as
to be even more scientifically
supported by
returning to that sad episode of
michael di michael what do you have what it is
deemed appropriate to do and it came to
mind like this but human and spontaneous to make
a contribution if this could be
possible even if I feared that this
could happen as in fact it was
so I thought point blank with
myself to make a phone call
in that of maranello in emilia romagna
where ferrari axis
this because because michael schumacher,
moreover, I am a fan of a
beautiful man he has been for many years
won several world titles
with the iron and they allowed me to
call to try to suggest to
whoever had the most title I am referring
above all to those who manage ferrari and
presidential intermediates to give a
modest suggestion of co,
it being
understood that my own suggestion of
tired could also not be accepted and the very modest origin
that I cannot represent and
whoever answered the phone
having dialed the number of the
maranello office first told me
that his but yesterday he was no longer one of their
drivers so it was not something that
they were interested in when they never
even understand very little and then having
asked to speak with the owner
of the company or with the president of the
company I was told that it
was not possible to do so because I
simply wanted to suggest the possibility
of an alternative to classical medicine
precisely due to the fact that it was known that
michael schumacher had and still has
three months almost four months
away the legend that it was on
December 29 last year the
removal of these madonnas following the
same path that he had
personally followed on 6 salvatore paladino
this path and the anathemas and was
taken I
could not do anything else I tried in
every way to insist I
telephoned again but they did
not listen to me in short, no one
answered me in the positive sense
there was no follow-up to
this call and still michael
schumacher is hospitalized in geneva
and he is not the hospital I don't know with what
fate
I hope that some sort of
divine suspension but far from his
existence
was probably what could have
happened to salvatore if he had been
subjected to that kind
of neurosurgery treatment that
awaited him as the only and exclusive
solution so that he could stay
alive or whatever. more can be said if you
think there is something else from the
judges they hugged me one by
one but they have not been with us
indeed here you make me remember here are the
words then they create that association to
say that they help you to remember
many of those who have criticized
Mrs. Maria infinite joy in the
video you made have emphasized
that these photographs where that yes yes can
glimpse the sai baba are synonymous
informative of who more a sort of
ambiguous environment that you can that that there is
here but I invite those who have doubts about the
weather not even to the ninth to believe in a
century do not believe in anything of all
that we say but simply car
try to understand by informing in
such a way as to have the two beating without
criticizing and attacking with witchcraft and
anything else the people who in reality are not
there but the most serious thing is that for a
sorcerer or they only take me
people do not know me but I
gave information to a lady with
a fibroid in the uterus that was
as big as a ball of times that was
increasing and who paid a m edico who
came from palermo to marsala and who
had not maiorella the visit went he
took the money and left
he gave him the medicines and continued to
increase the fibroid until his daughter
knowing me not admitted let's say
he had led to I gave him the
information and the daughter at her house
was helping her with the information that a
few months have passed by us and the
lady had nothing left when
the gentleman returned then who prayed
and money and will create
the internship with something not to I know who is a
gynecologist who had to treat that
fibroid when you visit her I notice that that one
was gone that huge
ball there was nothing normal anymore and
he said from which second she went
lady there are those who do the things they
should do they are second but not
only this I have treated many people in the town of
San Leone that is when
a little girl who had a nal fistula and
who had been martyred for years and
not three days the fistula napoli more
inf The connection has closed I treated a
girl at 11 years old who also
brought me back they had
thrown a bucket of boiling water or
in the groin and had to do them to
break the operation remove the skin
from the buttocks to be able to put it
there and in 15 days i will have more china says
how mister pino cammarata the same
thing
i treated a girl who had
breast pain and she changed
then she looked like a supermodel and first she looked like a
reggina who walked with her feet there are
all these things I have done I could
tell a doctor always from the same
family of the same parentage who
worked at the tower share palermo
at the civic of palermo had wade
was healed
the first is that unfortunately turner like
you are much better than me than everything
you are saying
even though I know the people in part
not at that time there was no
possibility to create
testimonials as well as
but what is happening therefore as if not
nothing had ever been done but let's leave it
alone I want to end up saying this
those people were part of a
catholic community that was that
of the madonna and black marians a
varied group the libya no human but real malians
the priest who managed them seeing that
these people they were no longer going
to church and they were having a
totally different mental dimension
because they were seeing
incredible things he said that I was born
like since I didn't take money
I didn't want anything and that these things
were done by fatah so I was
greased there you get to the most
brutal things to the most absurd things
since for forty years I have lost
my life and everything to help
people
and then it will really take Turin that
becomes a dog shot to those who do theater and
more than anything else they always become more real are
the words of the master jesus when he
said how long satan kicked
exactly it is not impossible in short
now if I do not pay me or they are seconds if I
pay myself I will take you a mess of money and
the search for leukemia and then to two
boys of 18 years and one of twenty is
already which there is the video of selena prigi
who had taken a [ __ ] hair
on the ground three were at 0 and the facade
was missing vito the right passed nando in
forty days and forty nights of
fasting followed by my information
with a whole family agree
she made the video that is
totally healed now another 20 years have passed
she has two wonderful children and she is
prettier than the first
thing it means you pieces of [ __ ]
that you criticize me for not
going to see videos because you do not try
to understand
with these people you can also talk
color call them and this is the trouble
we talk to nonsense we talk without
knowing people
if someone has something to criticize to
say about me come here and tell me
to my face if I could walk with
the asp and my back broken to get up
from here I have to get up re that even today
I can not walk well all the other
things have reconstituted themselves as if by a
miracle
if I could come from the tables that
have outraged me of course I at
their house for the purse way to tell him how he
allows you great scoundrel